LORENA TUHAY

Software Developer



ABOUT ME

After years of programming as a hobby, I'm currently finishing my degree in Software
Development. I consider myself a self-taught, proactive, curious, and creative person.
Many people I've worked with have described me as highly efficient. I thrive in team environments, as I see them as essential for enriching my knowledge and exploring different ways to achieve objectives.

VISIT PORTFOLIO Ituhay.github.io

CONTACT

Location: Buenos Aires, Argentina

Email: lorena.tuhay@gmail.com

Phone-WhatsApp: +54 9 11 6160-9490

LinkedIn profile: lorena-tuhay

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Software and Web Developer

2022 - Present

Design and development of static pages and interactive web applications. Configuration of hosting and domain. Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, WordPress, PrestaShop..

Freelance Proofreader and Academic Writing Consultant

2013 - Present

Correction and advice in the drafting and writing of academic texts such as theses, essays, dissertations, and academic reports.

Administrative Assistant at Boletín Oficial de la República Argentina and Ministerio de Seguridad de la Nación

2014 - 2023

Text writing and proofreading. Administration of databases used for the preparation of reports and statistics. General administrative tasks.

Community Manager and e-Commerce manager at Maier FotoPop 2019 - 2022

Content creation, copywriting, social media management. PrestaShop e-Commerce website design and maintenance.

Community Manager at Síntesis Ejecutiva

2010 - 2012

Content creation, copywriting, social media management.

SKILLS AND TECHNOLOGIES



EDUCATION AND LANGUAGES

Associate Degree in Software Development - UADE

2021 - Present

Approved courses: 16/20 - Average grade: 8.4/10

Literary Corrector - Instituto Superior en Letras Eduardo Mallea

2010 - 2013

Average grade: 9.29/10

English level: advanced (C2)